# Minal Bombatkar

# **UX** designer

https://minalbombatkar.com/

Open to relocate

Having valid German work permit
(Aufenthaltstitel)

**Contact:** 

Nuremberg, Germany 90429 +49 15163657851

bombatkar.minal@gmail.com

github.com/bombatkar-minal linkedin.com/in/minal-bombatkar

#### **Technical Skills:**

Wireframe tools Prototyping tools Adobe XD, Illustrator, Invision studio HTML, CSS, JS WordPress MS office

#### **UX Skills**:

Business requirements analysis
User analysis and user research
Personas
Customer journeys
Concept ideation
Information architecture
User flows
Wireframes, Mock-up's
Prototyping
User testing
Product development life cycle
Scrum planning and meeting, Agile
methodology
Presentations skills

## Certifications:

<u>Accenture</u>- Digital Skills User Experience

<u>LinkedIn learning</u>-Illustrator for Web Design Wireframing

<u>Gymnasium</u> Certificate of Excellence UX fundamentals Driven by the challenge to create simple, intuitive user experiences from conception to development. Able to execute all phases of the design process. Experience in the product development lifecycle of web and mobile applications by adopting agile methodology.

## **Experience:**

## **eLearning development Designer**

eNyota Ltd | May 2016 - Jun 2017

- Manage and co-ordinate in team for e-learning asset development. Crafted and interpreted, scripts supplied by colleagues and Subject Matter Experts and turn them in to informative and engaging learning materials.
- Converted existing training materials into online content
- Assisted in the development of course materials, assessment techniques, training videos and e-learning
- Used to follow Agile methodology and responsible for planning and conducting daily scrum meetings.

Fulltime Mother | Dec 2013 - April 2016

### **Assistant Professor**

VCACS College | Jan 2013 - Nov 2013

- Delivered lectures, seminars and tutorials. Designed the presentations and prepared the teaching materials.
- Organised workshops and professional development classes provided ongoing support to B.sc students.

### **Education:**

## CAREERFOUNDRY | March 2019 - Present | Germany

UX design certification course fulltime for 6 months.

Developed real-world projects during the course. Learn Design thinking process and user centric approach.

# **German language certification**

linguademia | May 2018 - Jan 2019 | Germany

German up to level B1: Fulltime course for 8 months and achieved the certificate of completion.

# **Master of Technology**

NMU | Aug 2009 - Sep 2011

Nanotechnology, Quantum Machines, Applied physics

# **Master of Science**

NMU | Aug 2007 - Jun 2009

Information technology, Web development, Programming language

#### **Bachelor of Science**

<u>Amravati University</u> | Jun 2004 – Jun 2007 Computer Science, Mathematics, Statistics